Partial Register of the Ronald MacArthur Hirst papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Stalingrad Files, 1929-2004 (Box 1-62)
  - Alphabetic name files, individuals
    - Hrabak, Dietrich, 1979 (Box 13)
    - Hube, Hans, 1966-1992 (Box 13)
    - Humbert, Gerhard, 1962-1997 (Box 13)
    - Hünemörder, Werner, 1970-1979 (Box 13)
    - Ilse, Wolfgang, 1985 (Box 13)
    - Jaenecke, Erwin, 1963-1992 (Box 13)
    - Jäger, Fritz, 1986 (Box 13)
    - Jagow, Wolf-Dietrich von, 1962-1963 (Box 13)
    - Jahnke, Gerhard, 1972 (Box 13)
    - Jahnke, Gustav, 1981-1986 (Box 13)
    - Jandl, Heinrich, 1978 (Box 13)
    - Jansson, Hans-Bernhard, 1981-1988 (Box 13)
    - Jaus, Otto, 1986-1992 (Box 13)
    - Jiras, Erich, 1978 (Box 13)
    - Jordan, Paul, 1968-1985 (Box 13)
    - Kaegler, Walter, undated (Box 13)
    - Kaiser, Franz, 1978-1992 (Box 13)
    - Kameke, Karl-Friedrich von, 1962-1990 (Box 13)
    - Kaminski, Werner, 1968-1973 (Box 13)
    - Kammeier, Ewald, 1973-1986 (Box 13)
    - Kämmerer, Gerhard, 1978 (Box 13)
    - Kaussler, Ludwig, 1980-1981 (Box 14)
    - Kayser, Hermann, 1967-1985 (Box 14)
    - Kayser, Josef, 1964-1991 (Box 14)
    - Keiner, Franz, 1971-1992 (Box 14)
    - Kessel, Alfred von, 1964-1975 (Box 14)
    - Ketelhodt, Christian-Ulrich von, 1976-1985 (Box 14)
    - Kimmel, Alfred, 1981 (Box 14)
    - Kirchbach, Hans Helmut, undated (Box 14)
    - Kirchgaesser, Gisbert, 1986 (Box 14)
    - Kirschofer, Andreas von, 1977-1981 (Box 14)
    - Kleikamp, Helmut, 1977-1985 (Box 14)
    - Klein, Erich, 2003-2004 (Box 14)
    - Klein, Heinrich, 1980-1981 (Box 14)
    - Klein, Paul, 1974-1993 (Box 14)
    - Kleine, Hasso, 1963-1973 (Box 14)
    - Klemm, F.W., 1971-1990 (Box 14)
    - Kling, Johann, 1992 (Box 14)
    - Klopsch, Friedrich, 1981 (Box 14)
    - Knetsch, Wilhelm, 1971-1975 (Box 14)
    - Knobelsdorff, Joachim von, 1991 (Box 14)
    - Knobloch, Gert von, 1986 (Box 14)
    - Köckritz, Kraft von, undated (Box 14)
    - Kohlar, Gerhard, 1984 (Box 14)
    - Kohler, Ottmar, 1969-1979 (Box 14)
    - Kohlermann, Otto, 1964-1974 (Box 14)
    - Kollmer, Rudolf, 1990 (Box 14)
    - Konetzke, Hubert, 1979-1986 (Box 14)
    - Koopmann, Hermann, 1982 (Box 14)
    - Köpsell, Martin, 1986 (Box 14)
    - Korfes, Otto, 1965-1985 (Box 14)
    - Kornatzki, Wilhelm von, 1992 (Box 14)
    - Korte, 1981 (Box 14)
    - Koziol, Friedrich, 1984-1986 (Box 14)
    - Kratsch, Günther, 1975-1986 (Box 14)
    - Krause, Fritz, 1979 (Box 14)
    - Krause, Fritz E., 1979-2003 (Box 14)
    - Kravogel, Helmut, 1986 (Box 14)
    - Kreiner, Herbert, 1985-1988 (Box 14)
    - Kreiser, Wilhelm, 1986-1991 (Box 14)
    - Krell, Rudolf, 1968 (Box 14)
    - Kress von Kressenstein, Hans-Karl, 1975-1977 (Box 14)
    - Kroiss, Fritz, 1992 (Box 14)
    - Krug, Wilhelm (?), 1979 (Box 14)
    - Krüger, Arthur, 2002 (Box 14)
    - Krumpen, Paul-Heinz, 1991-1992 (Box 14)
    - Kudicke, Helmut, 1972-1986 (Box 14)
    - Kuhr, Walter, undated (Box 14)
    - Kumpf, Franz, 1986 (Box 14)
    - Kunowski, Werner, 1965-1985 (Box 14)
    - Kurz, Georg, 1985-1988 (Box 14)
    - Kutzschenbach, 1974-1986 (Box 14)
    - Lamprecht, Karl, 1965-1980 (Box 14)
    - Lang, Karl, 1964-1981 (Box 14)
    - Langkeit, Willy, 1972-1980 (Box 15)
    - Lattmann, Martin, 1978-1992 (Box 15)
    - Ledig, Wolfgang, 1967-1986 (Box 15)
    - Lehmann, Georg, 1968 (Box 15)
    - Lehmann, Hermann, 1967-1983 (Box 15)
    - Lenski, Arno von, 1967-1991 (Box 15)
    - Lepper, Richard, 1968-1985 (Box 15)
    - Lerche, Friedrich, 1967-1986 (Box 15)
    - Leyser, Hans-Georg, 1964-1985 (Box 15)
    - Linden, Josef, 1969-1986 (Box 15)
    - Lindow, Hans-Gottfried, 1981-1986 (Box 15)
    - Löbbecke, Eberhard von, 1983-1992 (Box 15)
    - Loewenich, Wilhelm von, 1985 (Box 15)
    - Lohmann, Günther, 1979-1985 (Box 15)
    - Loose, Eduard, 1971-1972 (Box 15)
    - Löser, Hans-Joachim, 1969-1986 (Box 15)
    - Lossow, Erich von, 1979-1985 (Box 15)
    - Lossow, Jobst von, 1974-1990 (Box 15)
    - Lüben, Hermann, 1974-1991 (Box 15)
    - Lucke, Christian von, 1966-1985 (Box 15)
    - Lüde, Walter von, 1966-1985 (Box 15)
    - Ludwig, Aloys, 1979-1985 (Box 15)
    - Ludwig, Günther, 1979 (Box 15)
    - Lührs, Otto, 1981 (Box 15)
    - Luley, Friedrich, 1986 (Box 15)
    - Lungershausen, Hermann, 1979-1986 (Box 15)
    - Lüttichau, Wilhelm von, 1986 (Box 15)
    - Luttitz, Hans von, 1967-1977 (Box 15)
    - Luz, Helwig, 1972 (Box 15)
    - MacDonald, Paul, 1978-1986 (Box 15)
    - Mäder, Hellmuth, 1974-1991 (Box 15)
    - Magnus, Erich, 1961-2000 (Box 16)
    - Maier, 1979-1981 (Box 16)
    - Mangold, Gottfried, 1967-1986 (Box 16)
    - Manitz, Hans-Horst, 1970-1986 (Box 16)
    - Mannel, Ernst-Gottfried, 1977-1986 (Box 16)
    - Mannhardt, Johann, 1969-1986 (Box 16)
    - Manstein, Christoph von, 1989 (Box 16)
    - Mantey, Günter von, 1977-1985 (Box 16)
    - Marckstadt, Carl Otto, 1968-1986 (Box 16)
    - Marquard, 1977 (Box 16)
    - Maurer, Alois, 1986 (Box 16)
    - Mauss, Ernst, 1971 (Box 16)
    - Mayenburg, Ruth von, 1987 (Box 16)
    - Meinhof, Walter, 1981 (Box 16)
    - Meissner, Alfred, 1982-1983 (Box 16)
    - Meissner, Konstantin, 1977 (Box 16)
    - Menges, Otto-Wilhelm, undated (Box 16)
    - Menzel, Hubert, 1965-1986 (Box 16)
    - Mewes, Günther, 1985-1986 (Box 16)
    - Meyer, Arthur, 1986 (Box 16)
    - Meyer, Friedrich, 1990 (Box 16)
    - Meyer, Fritz, 1976 (Box 16)
    - Meyer, Georg, 1977-1982 (Box 16)
    - Meyer, Heinz, 1986 (Box 16)
    - Meyer, Nikolaus, 1970 (Box 16)
    - Middeldorf, Herbert, 1975-1976 (Box 16)
    - Moellendorf, Otto, undated (Box 16)
    - Mohr, Peter, 1964 (Box 16)
    - Moltke, Karl von, undated (Box 16)
    - Morzik, Fritz, 1972 (Box 16)
    - Mühlmeister, Adolf, 1980 (Box 16)
    - Müller, Rudolf, 1980-1992 (Box 16)
    - Müller, Siegfried, 1970-1990 (Box 16)
    - Müller, 1990 (Box 16)
    - Münch, Gerhard, 1973-1986 (Box 16)
    - Müncheberg, Paul, 1981-1982 (Box 16)
    - Mundt, Justus, 1979 (Box 16)
    - Münnich, Eckehart, 1986 (Box 16)
    - Münter, Otto, 1986-1990 (Box 16)
    - Mussil, Edgar, 1981-1992 (Box 16)
    - Mutius, Albrecht von, 1964-1985 (Box 16)
    - Nauck, Hellmuth, 1976-1978 (Box 16)
    - Neidhardt, Boris von, 1964-1975 (Box 16)
    - Neubert, Heinz, 1972-1990 (Box 16)
    - Neumann, Artur, 1967-1986 (Box 16)
    - Niemeyer, Friedrich-Franz, 1972-1977 (Box 16)
    - Nienstedt, Ernst, 1977-1978 (Box 16)
    - Nietmann, Kurt, 1969-1985 (Box 17)
    - Nitschke, Heinz, 1983-1986 (Box 17)
    - Nolcken, Eugen von, 1983 (Box 17)
    - Nostitz, Gustav Adolf, undated (Box 17)
    - Nuelle, Carlhans, 1981 (Box 17)
    - Obenaus, Gerhard, 1978-1985 (Box 17)
    - Ospel, Hans, 1986 (Box 17)
    - Ostarhild, Karl, 1971-1992 (Box 17)
    - Oster, Achim, 1965-1979 (Box 17)
    - Osterroht, Gotthilf, 1978 (Box 17)
    - Ostwalden, Hans Weber von, 1977-1986 (Box 17)
    - Ott, Walter, 1986 (Box 17)
    - Otte, Hans-Jürgen, 1981 (Box 17)
    - Otte, Heinz, 1983-1986 (Box 17)
    - Paltzo, Rudolf, 1978-1985 (Box 17)
    - Pässler, Siegfried, 1969-1990 (Box 17)
    - Pauer von Arlau, Ernst, 1965-1985 (Box 17)
    - Paulus, Friedrich von, 1959-1982 (Box 17)
      - Correspondence with family (Box 17)
      - Copy of manuscript from Ernst von Paulus, 1959 (Box 17)
    - Peifer, Rudolf, 1964-1975 (Box 17)
    - Petry, Heinz, 1972-1976 (Box 17)
    - Pezold, Bernd von, 1967-1986 (Box 17)
    - Pfeffer, Max, 1964-1991 (Box 17)
    - Pfeiffer, Jakob, 1964 (Box 17)
    - Pfeiffer, Philip Georg, 1971-1985 (Box 17)
    - Pfeuffer, Hans, 1988 (Box 17)
    - Pickel, Wilhelm, 1967-1978 (Box 17)
    - Pickert, Wolfgang, 1963-1991 (Box 18)
    - Plate, Klaus Henning von, 1970-1979 (Box 18)
    - Platen, Jürgen von, 1971-1985 (Box 18)
    - Plato, A.D. von, 1970 (Box 18)
    - Plessen, Wilhelm, 1966-1990 (Box 18)
    - Plock, Theodor, 1977-1986 (Box 18)
    - Plotho, Manfred von, 1965-1985 (Box 18)
    - Pogrell, Boguslaw von, 1992 (Box 18)
    - Pohl, Eberhard, 1964-1989 (Box 18)
    - Pohlman, Hartwig, 1965-1968 (Box 18)
    - Poschinski, Karl, 1986 (Box 18)
    - Pötschke, Herbert, 1971 (Box 18)
    - Probst, Josef, 1986 (Box 18)
    - Prüssner, Hermann, 1979-1980 (Box 18)
    - Purper, Otto Erich, 1980-1992 (Box 18)
    - Puttkamer, Jesco von, 1962-1992 (Box 18)
    - Radtke, Kurt Werner, 1984-1990 (Box 18)
    - Rantzau, Cai-Detlev, 1979 (Box 18)
    - Raven, Lothar von, 1990 (Box 18)
    - Reese, Wilhelm, 1981-1986 (Box 18)
    - Reh, Erwin te, 1990 (Box 18)
    - Reibnitz, Hans von, 1985 (Box 18)
    - Reichenau, 1963-1966 (Box 18)
    - Reichert, Raphael, 1976-1977 (Box 18)
    - Reichwald, Hans, 1970 (Box 18)
    - Reile, Oscar, 1967 (Box 18)
    - Reimer, Erich, 1978-1990 (Box 18)
    - Reinbrecht, Günther, 1990-1992 (Box 18)
    - Reinke, Siegfried, 1978-1981 (Box 18)
    - Renoldi, Otto Karl, 1961-1993 (Box 18)
    - Renschhausen, Karl-Ludwig, 1974 (Box 18)
    - Rentsch, Heinrich, 1985-1990 (Box 18)
    - Rettenmaier, Eberhard, undated (Box 18)
    - Reuber, Kurt, 1988-1992 (Box 18)
    - Reuss, Heinrich IV, Prince of, 1985 (Box 18)
    - Reuter, Fritz, 1984 (Box 18)
    - Rexroth, Christian, 1985 (Box 18)
    - Richthofen, Manfred von, 1990-1992 (Box 19)
    - Riebow, Günther, 1963-1972 (Box 19)
    - Riemer, Erich, 1978-1999 (Box 19)
    - Riggert, Friedrich, 1980 (Box 19)
    - Rochow, Hans, undated (Box 19)
    - Rodenburg, Carl, 1961-1993 (Box 19)
    - Röder, Johannes, undated (Box 19)
    - Roenne, Carl Ewald von, 1990 (Box 19)
    - Röhnisch, Walter, 1965-1971 (Box 19)
    - Rokitta Paul, 1967-1981 (Box 19)
    - Rom, Moritz von, 1980-1996 (Box 19)
    - Rönnefarth, Helmuth, 1965-1999 (Box 19)
    - Ronz, Anton, 1981 (Box 19)
    - Rosenthal, Hans, 1985 (Box 19)
    - Roske, Friedrich, 1963-1991 (Box 19)
      (2 files)
    - Rössler, August, 1979 (Box 19)
    - Roth, Joachim, 1972-1975 (Box 19)
    - Rothkirch von Pantehn, Kurt-Wilhelm, 1985-1989 (Box 19)
    - Rotsmann, Fritz Joachim von, 1964 (Box 19)
    - Rubach, Gerd, 1985 (Box 19)
    - Rumpf, Hermann, 1980-1985 (Box 19)
    - Rüthnick, Franz, 1979-1986 (Box 19)
    - Rydl, Friedrich, 1971 (Box 19)
    - Sachse, Horst, 1986 (Box 19)
    - Saint-Paul, Guy Le Tanneux von, undated (Box 19)
    - Sames, Karl, 1986 (Box 19)
    - Sanne, Werner, 1966-1993 (Box 20)
    - Sarrazin, Wilfrid, undated (Box 20)
    - Sauer, Heinz, 1977-1982 (Box 20)
    - Sauerbruch, Peter, 1964-1990 (Box 20)
    - Schaar, Georg, 1970 (Box 20)
    - Schaeffer, Hans-Joachim, 1972 (Box 20)
    - Schaeffer, Wilhelm, 1975 (Box 20)
    - Schall, Wolfgang, 1973-1991 (Box 20)
    - Scharenberg, Eberhard, 1965-1985 (Box 20)
    - Scharnweber, Adolf, 1969 (Box 20)
    - Scharping, Heinz, 1971-1999 (Box 20)
    - Schätz, Hans, 1986 (Box 20)
    - Schaumberg, Bernhard von, 1986 (Box 20)
    - Scheel, 1992 (Box 20)
    - Scheele, Alexander von, 1966-1971 (Box 20)
    - Scheidel, Norbert, 1986 (Box 20)
    - Schier, Philipp, 1986 (Box 20)
    - Schildknecht, Friedrich, 1964-1986 (Box 20)
    - Schill, Heinrich, 1977-1983 (Box 20)
    - Schimak, Anton, 1967-1972 (Box 20)
    - Schlessmann, Hermann, 1967-1986 (Box 20)
    - Schleswig-Holstein, Prince Friedrich Ferdinand von, 1968-1989 (Box 20)
    - Schlömer, Helmuth, 1962-1991 (Box 20)
    - Schmalschläger, Heinz, 1968-1976 (Box 20)
    - Schmid, Franz, 1972 (Box 20)
    - Schmid-Lossberg, Karl, 1965-1988 (Box 20)
    - Schmidt, Arthur (Box 20)
      - Adam book, undated (Box 20)
      - Below, Nicolaus von, 1963-1991 (Box 20)
      - Biographical, 1982-1991 (Box 21)
      - Burial, 1987 (Box 21)
      - Career, undated (Box 21)
      - Correspondence between Hirst and Schmidt (Box 21)
        - 1961-1969 (Box 21)
        - 1970-1973 (Box 21)
        - 1974-1979 (Box 21)
        - 1980-1986 (Box 21)
      - Family, 1968-1991 (Box 21)
      - Friends (Box 21)
        - Pre-World War I, 1963-1991 (Box 21)
        - AOK 6, 1983-1986 (Box 21)
      - Jaenecke Report, 1973 and undated (Box 21)
      - Legends about Stalingrad, undated (Box 21)
      - Manstein book, undated (Box 21)
      - Pickert, Wolfgang, 1965-1966 (Box 21)
      - Surrender, AOK 6, undated (Box 21)
      - Wieder book, undated (Box 21)
      - V. Armeekorps, 1991 (Box 21)
      - VI. Armeekorps, undated (Box 21)
      - XVIII. Armeekorps, undated (Box 22)
    - Schmidt, Eberhard, 1993 (Box 22)
    - Schmidt, Heinrich, 1986-1992 (Box 22)
    - Schmidt, Hermann, 1983 (Box 22)
    - Schmidt, Kurt, 1975 (Box 22)
    - Schmidt-Pauli, Egbert von, 1985 (Box 22)
    - Schmoll, Richard, 1983-1986 (Box 22)
    - Schnatz, Karl, 1986 (Box 22)
    - Schneider, Paul, 1983-1986 (Box 22)
    - Scholz, Günter, 1967-1990 (Box 22)
    - Scholz, Paul, 1978 (Box 22)
    - Schönberg-Hartenstein, Johannes von, 1993 (Box 22)
    - Schonfeldt, Joachim von, 1992 (Box 22)
    - Schott, Wilhelm, 1987 (Box 22)
    - Schraml, Franz, 1970-1985 (Box 22)
    - Schroeder, Martin, 1988-1990 (Box 22)
    - Schroerschwarz, Werner, 1964-1975 (Box 22)
    - Schröter, Heinz, 1964-1986 (Box 22)
    - Schubert, Conrad von, 1981- (Box 22)
    - Schuler von Senden, undated (Box 22)
    - Schultz, Rudolf, 1965-1967 (Box 22)
    - Schulze-Krantz, Ernst-Joachim, 1980-1982 (Box 22)
    - Schumann, Artur, 1984-2003 (Box 22)
    - Schumann, Kurt, 1986-1990 (Box 22)
    - Schuppan, Joachim, undated (Box 22)
    - Schwanbeck, Johannes, 1984 (Box 22)
    - Schwanenflug [empty] (Box 22)
    - Schwartz, Arthur, 1965-1977 (Box 22)
    - Schwarz, Karl, 1975-2001 (Box 22)
    - Schweinitz, Georg von, 1964-1998 (Box 22)
    - Schwerin, Richard von, 1962-2004 (Box 22)
    - Seebach, Christoph von, 1985 (Box 22)
    - Seeber, Hans, 1980 (Box 22)
    - Seggelke, Karl, 1969-1986 (Box 22)
    - Segreff, Robert, 1986 (Box 22)
    - Seidel, Heinrich, 1977-1981 (Box 22)
    - Selle, Herbert (Box 21)
      - Correspondence, 1964-1975 (Box 21)
      - Correspondence and background material, 1976-1990 (Box 23)
    - Senfft von Pilsach, Wolfgang, 1985 (Box 23)
    - Sewing, Dietrich, 1968-1978 (Box 23)
    - Seydlitz-Kurzbach, Walther von, 1962-1986 (Box 23)
    - Seydlitz und Ludwigsdorf, Friedrich von, 1962 (Box 23)
    - Seyffertitz, Theobald, undated (Box 23)
    - Sichart, Hans-Karl, undated (Box 23)
    - Sieckenius, Rudolf, 1964-1991 (Box 23)
    - Sixt von Arnim, Hans-Heinrich, 1971-1992 (Box 23)
    - Smend, Heinrich, 1970-1991 (Box 24)
    - Snowadski, Roderich, 1977 (Box 22)
    - Sommerlad, Wilhelm, 1967-1984 (Box 22)
    - Spangenberg, Hans Christoph, 1979 (Box 22)
    - Spannagel, Hans, 1980-1986 (Box 22)
    - Spetzler, Eberhard, 1977-1983 (Box 22)
    - Spiegelberg, Hans-Emil, 1972-1985 (Box 22)
    - Spodeck, Paul, 1976 (Box 22)
    - Spoerhase, Otto, 1978-1979 (Box 22)
    - Spohr, Ludwig, 1981-1986 (Box 22)
    - Sprenger, Leo, undated (Box 22)
    - Stabenau, Willy Georg, 1969-1986 (Box 24)
    - Stahlberg, Alexander von, 1990-1992 (Box 24)
    - Stange, Justus, 1964-1993 (Box 24)
    - Stark, Karl, 1986 (Box 24)
    - Steffler, Hans, 1978-1991 (Box 24)
    - Stegner, Ludwig, 1971-1984 (Box 24)
    - Steidle, Luitpold, 1961-1984 (Box 24)
    - Steiner, Helmut, 1980-1990 (Box 24)
    - Steinhoff, Heinrich, 1978 (Box 24)
    - Steinmetz, Bernhard, 1963-1981 (Box 24)
    - Steinmeyer, Robert, 1971-1986 (Box 24)
    - Stempel, H., 1974 (Box 24)
    - Stempel, Joachim, 1999-2002 (Box 24)
    - Stempel, Richard, 1966-1992 (Box 24)
    - Sterz, Reinhold, 1978-1992 (Box 24)
    - Stiotta, Max, undated (Box 24)
    - Stockhausen, Hans Ludwig, 2003-2004 (Box 24)
    - Stolberg-Stolberg, Bernhard, 1985-1990 (Box 24)
    - Stolberg-Stolberg, Wolfgang, 1990 (Box 24)
    - Stolz, Karl Heinz, 1986 (Box 24)
    - Stösslein, Herbert, 1964-1983 (Box 24)
    - Strachwitz, Hyazinth, 1978 (Box 24)
    - Strauss, Franz Josef, 1990 (Box 24)
    - Strecker, Karl, 1961-1991 (Box 24)
    - Strehlke, Ernst-Günther, undated (Box 24)
    - Stubhahn, Felix, 1992 (Box 24)
    - Stübichen, Ernst, 1965-1989 (Box 24)
    - Stumpff, Leberecht von, undated (Box 24)
    - Tarnow, Martin, 1973 (Box 25)
    - Taube, Alexander von, 1977 (Box 25)
    - Tempsky, Christoph-Eberhard von, 1963 (Box 25)
    - Thadden, Henning von, undated (Box 25)
    - Theloe, Gerhard, 1982 (Box 25)
    - Theysohn, Karl-Heinz, 1964-1990 (Box 25)
    - Thielmann, Heinrich, undated (Box 25)
    - Thomas, Erich, 1989-2002 (Box 25)
    - Thunert, Eberhard, 1966-1991 (Box 25)
    - Thurn und Taxis, Gabriel von, 1990 (Box 25)
    - Tiedemann, Hans-Georg von, 1980-1985 (Box 25)
    - Tobias, Ernst, 1980-1990 (Box 25)
    - Toepke, Günter, 1969-1988 (Box 25)
    - Toursel, Otto, 1979-1986 (Box 25)
    - Treskow, Harald, undated (Box 25)
    - Trier, Josef, 1988 (Box 25)
    - Trömner, Walter, 1985 (Box 25)
    - Tröster, Oswald, 1988 (Box 25)
    - Trott zu Solz, Christoph, undated (Box 25)
    - Tschischwitz, Hans von, 1977-1985 (Box 25)
    - Tümpling, Hans von, 1981-1986 (Box 25)
    - Tzschöckell, Paul, 1986 (Box 25)
    - Uhr, Johannes, 1988 (Box 25)
    - Ullrich, August, 1967-2002 (Box 25)
    - Ulreich, Karl, 1963-1979 (Box 25)
    - Underberg, Carl, 1965 (Box 25)
    - Vaas, Anton, 1990 (Box 25)
    - Varbelow, Kurt, 1978 (Box 25)
    - Vassoll, Ulrich, 1966-1991 (Box 25)
    - Vester, Herbert, 1988-1989 (Box 25)
    - Vetter von der Lilie, Karl, 1990 (Box 25)
    - Viertel, Karl, 1978-1985 (Box 25)
    - Vietinghoff-Riesch, Arnold von, 1985 (Box 25)
    - Vietze, Heinz, 1985 (Box 25)
    - Vitzthum von Eckstädt, Heinrich, 1965-2002 (Box 25)
    - Voget, Heinrich, 1982 (Box 25)
    - Vogt, Heinrich, 1970-1981 (Box 25)
    - Voss, Adolf, 1985-1986 (Box 25)
    - Wagemann, Eberhard, 1971-1986 (Box 25)
    - Wagner, Hans, 1992-2004 (Box 25)
    - Waldersee, Alfred von, 1971-1984 (Box 25)
    - Wangenheim, Konrad von, 1986 (Box 25)
    - Warmuth, Karl, 1977-1978 (Box 25)
    - Weber, Artur, 1963-1985 (Box 25)
    - Weber, Johann, 1972-1982 (Box 25)
    - Wechmar, Albrecht von, 1966-1981 (Box 25)
    - Wedel, Lupold von, 1990 (Box 25)
    - Wegener, Rolf, 1983 (Box 25)
    - Wehr, Kurt, 1984 (Box 25)
    - Weichs, Maximilian von, 1991 (Box 25)
    - Weiher, Heinz, 1990 (Box 25)
    - Werkmeister, Johannes, 1976-1982 (Box 25)
    - Werder, Richard von, 1992 (Box 25)
    - Werner, Otto, 1986 (Box 25)
    - West, Hans-Georg, 1971-1990 (Box 25)
    - Westphalen zu Fürstenberg, Friedrich Carl von, 1991-1993 (Box 26)
    - Wieder, Joachim, 1965-1992 (Box 26)
    - Wietersheim, Wend von, 1967-1991 (Box 26)
    - Wilde von Wildemann, Wilhelm, 1959-1985 (Box 26)
    - Wilhelm, Franz, 1986-1990 (Box 26)
    - Wilke, Alfred, 1980 (Box 26)
    - Wilke, Erwin, 1975-1990 (Box 26)
    - Wilkens, Albert, 1964-1971 (Box 26)
    - Willers, Hans-Jürgen, 1980 (Box 26)
    - Willig, Karl, 1971-1977 (Box 26)
    - Wilutzky, Horst, 1969-1986 (Box 26)
    - Winckel, Hans-Peter aus dem, 1973-1986 (Box 26)
    - Winterfeld, Wilfried von, 1985 (Box 26)
    - Wintzingerode, Wilko von, 1963-1993 (Box 26)
    - Witte, Karl-Heinz, 1986 (Box 26)
    - Woelfel, Erich, 1968-1979 (Box 26)
    - Woellwarth-Lauterburg, Konrad, undated (Box 26)
    - Woerz, Alfred, 1986 (Box 26)
    - Wölfert, Edgar, 2002 (Box 26)
    - Wolff, Wilhelm, 1978 (Box 26)
    - Wrisberg, Ernst von, undated (Box 26)
    - Wulz, Hans, 1966-1991 (Box 26)
    - Zank, Horst, 1986-2004 (Box 26)
    - Zedtwitz, Hans von, 1965 (Box 26)
    - Zielisch, Hans, 1967-1986 (Box 26)
    - Zimmermann, Heinz, 1975-1989 (Box 26)
    - Zimmermann, Johannes, 1981 (Box 26)
    - Zimmermann, Werner, 1965-1980 (Box 26)
    - Zitzewitz, Coelestin von, 1962-1992 (Box 26)
    - Zitzewitz, Georg Wilhelm von, 1991 (Box 26)
    - Zitzewitz, Jürgen, 1978-1991 (Box 26)
    - Zuber, Karl, 1986 (Box 26)
    - Zuckschwerdt, Gerhard, 1975-1978 (Box 26)
    - Zülow, Friedrich von, 1985 (Box 26)
  - Name files, grouped by division commander
    Outgoing correspondence from Hirst.
    - Angern, Günther (16th Armored Division), 1974-1981 (Box 27)
    - Arenstorff-Oyle, Hans-Adolf (60th Infantry Division-Mot.), 1971-1981 (Box 27)
    - Arndt, Karl, 1968-1971 (Box 27)
    - Arnold, Wilhelm, 1966-1982 (Box 27)
    - Bader, Robert, 1966-1981 (Box 27)
    - Bässler, Johannes (14th Armored Division), 1964-1975 (Box 27)
    - Daniels, Alexander von (376th Infantry Division), 1971-1981 (Box 27)
    - Deboi, Heinrich (44th Infantry Division), 1975-1981 (Box 27)
    - Drebber, Moritz von (297th Infantry Division) (Box 27)
    - Ebner, Hans Josef (Box 27)
    - Gablenz, Eccard von (Box 27)
    - Hartmann, Alexander von (Box 27)
    - Heitz, Walter (8th Army Corps), 1963-1981 (Box 27)
    - Hube, Hans (XIV Panzerkorps) (Box 27)
    - Jaenecke, Erwin (4th Army Corps), 1963-1981 (Box 27)
    - Kayser, Hermann (4th Army Corps), 1966-1981 (Box 27)
    - Korfes, Otto (295th Infantry Division), 1964-1981 (Box 27)
    - Langkeit, Willy,(14th Armored Division), 1979 (Box 27)
    - Lattmann, Martin (Box 27)
    - Lenski, Arno von (24th Armored Division), 1962-1981 (Box 28)
    - Lepper, Richard (ARKO 6), 1962-1976 (Box 28)
    - Leyser, Hans-Georg(29th Infantry Division-Mot.), 1961-1981 (Box 28)
    - Mäder, Hellmuth (297th Infantry Division), 1965-1981 (Box 28)
    - Magnus, Erich (389th Infantry Division), 1961-1981 (Box 28)
    - Müller, Siegfried (Doctor, 8th Army Corps), 1966-1981 (Box 28)
    - Pauer und Arlau, Ernst (197th Infantry Division), 1965-1971 (Box 28)
    - Paulus, Friedrich von (Armee Oberkommando 6), 1965-1977 (Box 28)
    - Pfeffer, Max (297th Infantry Division), 1964-1982 (Box 28)
    - Pfeiffer, Georg (94th Infantry Division), 1971-1981 (Box 28)
    - Pickert, Wolfgang,(9th Flakdivision-Mot.), 1975-1981 (Box 28)
    - Rodenburg, Carl (76th Infantry Division), 1964-1981 (Box 28)
    - Roske, Friedrich (71st Infantry Division), 1963-1977 (Box 28)
    - Sanne, Werner (100 Jaegerdivision), 1962-1978 (Box 28)
    - Schlömer, Helmut (3rd Infanteriedivision), 1961-1981 (Box 28)
    - Schmidt, Arthur (Armee-Oberkommando 6), 1961-1981 (Box 28)
  - Correspondence files, general and alphabetical
    - General, arranged chronologically
      - 1991-1997 (Box 29)
      - 1999 (Box 29)
      - 2000 (Box 29)
      - 2001 (Box 29)
      - 2002 (Box 29)
      - 2003 (Box 29)
      - 2004 (Box 29)
    - Allen, Jeffrey, 2001 (Box 29)
    - Alte Kamerad (Stuttgart), 1973 (Box 29)
    - American Institute for Contemporary German Studies, Johns Hopkins University, 1993 (Box 29)
    - Beevor, Anthony, 1996-2000 (Box 29)
    - Below-Breuer, Elke von, 2000-2003 (Box 29)
    - Bibliothek für Zeitgeschichte, Stuttgart, 1966-1993 (Box 29)
    - Blennemann, Ulrich, 1992 (Box 29)
    - British Broadcasting Corporation, 1997-2001 (Box 29)
    - Burdick, Charles, 1989-1999 (Box 29)
    - Cavanaugh, Dennis, 1977-1992 (Box 29)
    - CBS, Inc., 1992-1993 (Box 29)
    - Chandler, David, 1985 (Box 29)
    - Clark, Alan, 1970 (Box 29)
    - Craig, William, 1969-2001 (Box 30)
    - Damerau, Helmut (Deutsches Soldatenjahrbuch), 1972-1982 (Box 30)
    - Deutsche Dienststelle (WASt), Berlin, 1965-1986 (Box 30)
    - Deutsches Rotes Kreuz, 1970-1990 (Box 30)
    - Düsing, Maria, 1981-1984 (Box 30)
    - Feldman, Robert S., 1991-1992 (Box 30)
    - Frankfurter Allgemeine Zeitung, 1973 (Box 30)
    - Frieser, Karl-Heinz, 1982-1985 (Box 30)
    - Gallagher, Matthew, 1973 (Box 30)
    - Görlitz, Walter, 1967-1969 (Box 30)
    - Hartog, Peter den, 1971 (Box 30)
    - Hinrichsen, Peter, 2001-2002 (Box 30)
    - Hofmann, Peter, 1993 (Box 30)
    - Hümmelchen, Dr., 1968 (Box 30)
    - Jukes, Geoffrey, 1968 (Box 30)
    - Kagan, Simon, 1997-2003 (Box 30)
    - Kehrig, Manfred (Bundesarchiv-Militärarchiv), 1964-1988 (Box 30)
    - Kerr, Walter, 1982 (Box 30)
    - Library of Congress (Washington, DC), 1986 (Box 30)
    - Mark, Jason, 2003 (Box 30)
    - Massignani, Alessandro, 1990-2000 (Box 30)
    - National Archives (United States)
      - 1970-1983 (Box 30)
      - 1984-1990 (Box 31)
    - Peters, Hermann, 1983 (Box 31)
    - Rensing, A., 1968-1971 (Box 31)
    - Rothfels, Hans, 1966 (Box 31)